We're in LA and um I'm not famous and I
I'm so sorry. Um [laughter]
I know. Um but if it feels like you've
seen me before, it's because I look like
every NBA referee, [snorts]
[laughter]
right? Don't I look like I should be
running backwards with a whistle? You
know,
but I'm from Wisconsin, so I'd be like,
"That's a foul. Sorry." You know,
[laughter]
I'm so sorry. I'd be sending games into
overtime just because I hate goodbyes,
you know.
I just want to be together, you guys.
You know, that's all. Um, yeah, I'm from
Wisconsin. And, uh, when I say that, I
just want to let you guys know I'm a
little drunk right now.
[cheering]
Yeah, it just is what it is. And I don't
even think that Wisconsin has an accent.
I think we just learned how to talk from
drunk adults.
I do. I think my dad was like, "Do you
want to go to kindergarten today?"
[laughter]
And I was like, "Elmento Oop."
Yeah. [laughter]
I was getting hammered last night. Uh
cuz that's what I do. And
I was getting hammered and this guy next
to me at the bar, he go he goes, "Buddy,
what are you drinking?" And I go, "Every
day."
[laughter]
And I don't know. I just I do drink
every day. And I Sorry. Um
I don't know. If you have a liver, I
want it. Uh
I do. I have a friend. He's got type 1
diabetes. That's like a real serious
problem, right? And he's got this
medical device that's attached to his
body. And I was like, "Oh, what is
that?" He goes, "Oh," he goes, "I test
my blood sugar and I hitting this
button. It gives me insulin, the drug
that I need to feel better." I was like,
"Oh my god, that's a great idea. I'm
going to do that."
And he was like, "What?" And he came
over to my house a week later. He's
like, "What are you doing?" I go, "Oh, I
bought a keychain breathalyzer off of
Amazon.com. This tests my blood alcohol
and it lets me know if I need the drug
that makes me feel better."
He was like, "That's not how it works."
I was like, "Oh, it does.
I was like 008 feeling great
[laughter]
0.11 having fun
0.15 I can drive.
>> Yeah. No, don't drink and drive you
guys. Uh don't
that's my whole thing is don't you know
while we're at it don't text while
driving. you know, you guys are like my
best friends here, you know.
No, don't text while driving. I was
reading about that the other day while I
was driving and
it's like, man, I'm glad I'm not texting
right now. That be [laughter]
that'd be so dangerous.
I don't know. I love I love I want to
text while I'm driving cuz I just I just
want to connect. Like I I do I want to
connect with people all the time. And I
know that's weird, right? Like I walk
down the street and I'll be like, "Hi."
Hey, and people are like, "No,
don't do that." All right. [laughter]
I have a problem when I can't connect.
Uh, have you guys ever been on a really
long car drive? Do you know what I'm
talking about? Like, I'm not talking
like 6 hours. I'm talking like eight
hours, right? Like, and you're on hour 6
and a half and none of your friends are
answering the phone because maybe you
are a lot. [laughter]
All right. That happened to me last
week. I was an hour six and a half.
Nobody. Nobody's answering. I was I was
just going crazy. And finally I see a
state trooper and he's just like hiding
in the median and I just sped up a
bunch.
[laughter]
Yeah. And he was like I was like guess
who's going to talk. [laughter]
He was like do you know why I pulled you
over? I was like cuz I have an awful
need to connect. [laughter]
He was like what? And I was like I
haven't talked to anybody all day and I
saw you and I was like he'll talk to me.
And he was like that's the craziest
thing I've ever heard in my life. And
he's like, "That's that's nuts." He's
like, "I'm going to have to write you a
ticket that's like $175." And I was
like, "Well, my therapist charges 200 an
hour." [laughter]
So, how much time do you got?
[applause]
He was like, "Have you been drinking?" I
was like, "I could grab a beer."
[laughter]
And now he's my friend on Facebook. So
yeah, I don't know. I'm I'm not angry.
Uh I know everybody's angry. No, I'm
just I'm just not. Uh if you go on
social media, right, everybody's like,
"If you're not angry, you're part of the
problem." I'm like, I am on so much
Zolop. [laughter]
Do you understand? This is me angry,
[laughter]
which is actually terrifying, [laughter]
right? I'm going to get you.
I can't be scary if I tried. I could
show up in your bedroom tonight at 3:30
in the morning with a menacing shadow
cast over half of my face wearing a
leather butcher's apron holding an
idling chainsaw and your first thought
would be like, "Oh, maybe he's making an
ice sculpture. [laughter]
I bet it's a penguin."
[laughter]
Oh, I I love everybody. I Oh my god.
Have you guys ever uh Have you guys ever
been gay? Anybody in here?
Oh my god, I love that community. I used
to live in a gay community and I loved
it. It was like the Midwest cuz guys
would just come up to you and be like,
"How you doing?" I'd be like, "Pretty
good." [laughter]
You want to grab a beer? Sure do.
You know, I loved it there. You know,
no, I if you're if you're gay, oh my
god, I love you. I I will hug you till
you don't want it. Um, [laughter]
I'll uh I'll be vulnerable. I'll share
my truth. Okay. Uh, I was doing the
Tonight Show starring Jimmy Fallon and
Yeah. Woo. And the lead actor on the
show that night was hunky actor Ryan
Gosling.
>> Those weren't even your mouths making
that noise. Those were your ovaries
going. [laughter]
>> Right. Like I when I saw him, I
ovulated. Like I
I was I was walking in the makeup room
and he breezed past me and I like I saw
him and my my eyes locked with his icy
blue eyes and he goes, "Hi." And I tried
to say hi, but just my mouth goes.
Like mentally I was like, "If you're a
bird, I'm a bird."
Do you understand how confusing that
moment was for me?
I'm 45 years old. I've never been gay in
my life until right then.
And then I was the most gay. I pictured
my whole gay future with Ryan.
[laughter] We were working out together,
smiling at each other, wiping down in
the elliptical. [laughter]
You know, I was like, I got to fly home
and tell my dad. [laughter] And I know
exactly how it's going to go. I'm going
to I'm going to fly home. I'll be like,
"Dad, I'm gay and you need to accept
me." My dad's he's a conservative
gentleman. And he's going to be like,
"Poof, steam. I don't know if I like
that." And I'm like, "Dad, I'm gay for
Ryan Gosling." My dad's going to be
like, "Damn it.
Now I'm gay.
This guy does it to everybody."
I hope I haven't offend anybody. Uh I I
just That's my nightmare. Um [laughter]
no, comedians are always like, "We got
to be edgy." I'm like, "Not me.
[laughter]
I don't want to do that. I hate
conflict." Unless you guys like it and
then I love you.
Like whatever you like. [laughter]
I'm so careful with my words that I
don't even say things that you can say.
Like I like All right. I was on an
airplane recently and I sat down next to
this gal and she tapped me on the
shoulder and she goes, "Pardon me." She
goes, "But my name is Tanisha." And she
goes, "I'm a big fan of your stand-up
comedy." And I was like, "Oh my god,
Tanisha, thank you." And she goes, "And
wow, I watch all your videos on
Instagram and Tik Tok." And she goes,
"Wow, you do wear black t-shirts every
single day." And I said, "Yes, I do wear
this colored t-shirt every day."
[laughter]
And she laughed like you did. And she
goes, "You know, you can say black." And
I go, "I know.
And I know you know." [laughter]
And she's laughing. She goes, "Say it."
She goes, "Say black." And I was like,
"Well, I wouldn't say it like that."
She goes, "Say it." And I was like, "I'm
I'm going to."
She goes, "Say it." And I I go, "Black
history month."
[laughter]
And now she's my friend on Facebook.
That was a good one.
>> Yeah. Whoa. You can probably tell that I
listen to a lot of hardcore gangster
rap,
right? I love to I love to listen to it.
I love to sing along to it, right? But
I'll tell you what, I sing almost every
word. Not one. Okay. I don't know. And
if you do, don't.
What I do is I say my name in its place.
I'll be like, "If you don't know, now
you know." Peter
[laughter]
wicked wick Peter please
[groaning]
all day. Peter
[laughter]
Peter's in Paris. You know, [laughter]
this guy came up to me last night after
the show and he goes, "Nuckles, my
dude." He goes, "You're my Peter." And I
go, "Whoa, that's my word."
>> All right, you guys. I'm Pete Lee. Thank
you so much for being a great girl. Hey,
how are you guys? [cheering]
>> Good. Great. Great. I'm also doing
great. I just got out of a relationship,
so [cheering]
yeah. I know. It's been great. I've had
a lot of really supportive friends, you
know. I've had a lot of really
supportive guy friends. [laughter]
Just a bunch of guys that I was like, I
didn't even know we're friends like
that. [laughter]
They do get mad though. One of them was
like, it feels like you're friend-zoning
me. [laughter]
I was so nice to you. I took you to the
airport.
It's like, my mom takes me to the
airport all the time [laughter]
and I never [\h__\h] her.
>> [laughter]
>> She's never like, "Your mom's owning
me." [laughter]
What the [\h__\h]
Dating is going to be really hard for me
because I am banned from dating sites.
[laughter]
I'm banned from Bumble and Tinder. Uh,
and I'll tell you what happened. I'll
tell you. I was drunk one night and I
was on Bumble and Tinder and for my bio
I wrote, "I'm going to find your family
and I'm going to kill them." [laughter]
[laughter]
And guys still responded.
They'd be like, "What are you up to
tonight?" [laughter]
I was like, "I don't know. Where does
your family live?
That's what I was like. Men are way too
horny. Okay. They're way too horny. Like
I think I think men are willing to say
and do anything when they're horny, you
know? Yeah. Like I think the biggest
feminist I've ever met is just a horny
guy at a bar at 2:00 a.m. [laughter]
They're willing to give up their right
to vote to go home with you. [laughter]
And some of them do. They're in jail.
[laughter]
>> [laughter]
>> No, I've been horny, too. I've been
watching porn, and so have you. Uh,
[laughter]
it's not just me racking up 70 million
views per video. Okay,
I think it's hard to watch porn as a
woman, right? Cuz porn's very
unrealistic, you know? Like, I was
watching this porn the other day that
said, "Fucking the babysitter while my
wife is in the shower.
>> [laughter]
>> I was like, "Why is the babysitter here
if both parents are home?"
[laughter]
And who's watching this baby? [laughter]
No, I'm doing fine. I'm dating women
now, WHICH HAS BEEN It's been scary. Uh,
[laughter]
women are scary cuz I think the scariest
thing a man can do to you on a first
date is he will, you know, like follow
you home and kill you. [laughter]
Cuz guys are so goofy like that.
They're so silly. [laughter]
But a woman on a first date will just
out of nowhere be like, "So, what's your
relationship with her parents like?"
[laughter]
And I'm like, "Uh, I think you should
kill me. [laughter]
This is [\h__\h] awful.
[laughter]
I don't know. I'm doing fine.
I'm doing fine. I'm in therapy. Anyone
in therapy?
It's been it's been great. Going to
therapy is great. Uh I I am Asian and my
parents asked me why I go to therapy and
I was like, "Oh, do you remember when I
was a kid?" [laughter]
And you guys raised me. Um, [laughter]
that's it.
No, you were there. I mean, not
emotionally,
[laughter]
but you're around.
No, my parents are great. I hang out
with my dad a lot. Not cuz we're close.
We just have a mutual friend in common.
My mom. [laughter]
So, we hang.
My dad's great. He always talks to me
like we're two strangers who met at a
party and there's a lull in the
conversation. [laughter]
He's always like, "So,
how old are you?"
[cheering and laughter]
I'm like, "Don't worry about it. It's my
birthday party." But [laughter]
no, my parents are great. They do treat
all my childhood trauma like the North
Korean government treats their problems.
You know, they're always like, "You're
not sad. It's just Western propaganda."
[laughter]
I'm like, "Great, we figured it out."
Uh, [laughter]
that's great. I don't know. I've been
talking about my breakup in therapy.
Breakups are sad, right? Like, have you
guys ever been on the train and you're
like, "I think I'm going to cry on this
subway right now." You know? And then
like the guy sitting in front of you is
like, "Oh, yeah. That's what I get off
on." [laughter]
and you're like, "Everything reminds me
of him." [laughter]
[laughter]
I was on the train the other day and I
was listening to this Eda James song and
there's a line in the song where she
goes, "Something deep in my soul said,
"Cry, girl." And I was like, "Oh my god,
I think I'm going to cry." Uh, but it's
really hard to listen to blues and cry
about a guy who's in a pickle ball
league.
Those [laughter]
songs are written about men who work in
mines, okay? [laughter]
Not some guy who still takes gummy
vitamins.
I'm not going to cry about a guy who
can't swallow a pill. Okay, [laughter]
I'm doing better now. I hooked up with a
really hot guy recently.
>> Yeah, I know. It was great. He's the
kind of hot where he dates models, you
know, and then after we hooked up, he
goes, "I just want to be careful how we
go about this because you're not like
the other women I date. You're like a
real person."
Yeah.
It's like men don't know where to end a
sentence. [laughter]
Every guy I've dated will be like,
"You're the most beautiful woman in the
world." to me. [laughter]
It's like, who cares about your opinion,
dude? [laughter]
I did like that line cuz it's such a
[\h__\h] boy line, right? Like, you're so
real. I'm just not ready for something
real is [\h__\h] boy 101. [laughter]
Cuz every [\h__\h] boy acts like they're
really deep and vulnerable. Uh, but some
sort of gypsy curse has made them have
meaningless sex for the rest of their
lives. [laughter]
[laughter]
They all act like when they were 11, a
big Scottish man with a beard came up to
them and was like, "You're a [\h__\h] boy,
HARRY." [laughter]
Now they have no choice to get up.
[laughter]
I moved to New York recently. I've been
here for a year. New York's great. I
moved from Texas. New York's very
different. Yeah, it's very different. I
think it's very progressive, you know. I
think maybe things are getting a bit too
progressive. Um, [laughter]
clap if you think things are getting too
progressive. [applause]
Usually white guys are like, I'm going
to clap on the train later.
[laughter]
Not you, man.
Front row. [laughter]
No, I agree with you. I'm also a racist
or whatever. Um, [laughter]
I don't know.
I do think things are getting too
progressive. I got in trouble the other
day for using the word homeless. This
guy was like, "You can't say that. You
have to say people without housing." And
I was like, "Dude, I don't think their
problem is marketing.
[laughter]
It's not like I called him a house
[\h__\h]
[laughter]
Got away with it in Williamsburg, baby.
All right. [laughter]
[cheering]
No, I love homeless people. I love
homeless people. I think homeless people
can get away with things that a guy with
a mortgage could never [\h__\h] pull off.
[laughter]
Like I was outside this bar one time. I
had a cigarette. I didn't have a
lighter. And this homeless guy came up
to me and he said, "A pretty girl never
has to light her own cigarette." And he
lit my cigarette and he lit my friend's
cigarette and he didn't light my other
friend's cigarette and just left.
[laughter]
It was incredible. [laughter]
It was so good. She quit smoking.
It's amazing. [laughter]
I do like smoking cigarettes and people
who don't smoke don't get it. Like my
friends who don't smoke are always like,
"Is it worth it? Is smoking worth it?"
Let me tell you how worth it smoking is.
[laughter]
Some women smoke when they're pregnant.
That's how worth it smoking is.
[laughter]
I smoked when I was pregnant. Everything
turned out fine.
>> [laughter]
>> I got an abortion,
[laughter]
you know. And sometimes people get mad
when I tell that joke and I I just I
just let them know that it it was a gay
baby. [laughter]
[laughter]
>> I used to tell that joke in Texas and
people would get mad and I'd be like,
"Dude, the baby was on my property so I
shot him.
All right. Thank you guys so much. I'm
Casey. Thanks. [cheering]
>> It's nice crowd though. Nice, beautiful
white people, man. [\h__\h] yeah. I'm all
about it, man. Listen, I've been
traveling this country a lot and I've
been learning about the different layers
of white people. Yeah, [laughter] you
guys are not all the same, okay? Don't
let anyone ever [\h__\h] tell you that
cuz I've been to some places that have
shown me differently. I went to Vermont
[laughter]
and I saw the craziest [\h__\h] in Vermont.
I saw people playing Frisbee. [laughter]
>> Yeah. No dogs.
[laughter]
Not a dog in sight.
Yeah. It was humans
back and forth. Just [\h__\h]
[laughter]
throw it back, man. Throw it back. Throw
it back. Throw it back. Throw back.
Yeah. [\h__\h] yeah. [\h__\h] got him. [\h__\h]
yeah, dude. [\h__\h] yeah. You know, you
ready for this one? You ready for
[laughter]
me? [\h__\h] up. I was staring at that
[\h__\h] the whole time. Just like
I saw, man, the wildest [\h__\h] in Vermont,
man. I saw a roller ski team and [\h__\h] I
didn't even know they got down like
that. I saw [\h__\h] a rowing team, too,
in the [\h__\h] water. I felt like I was
in a goddamn allergy commercial. I was
like, "What the [\h__\h] is this? What is
this place, man?" Had me all confused,
dude.
>> [laughter]
>> We got some wild places in this country,
man. I went to this place called
Springfield, Missouri. Yeah,
we don't need them. [\h__\h] them. Okay.
Like,
it's [\h__\h] up out there. I was
terrified, man. I was flying into
Springfield, Missouri. I saw no skyline,
just fields, right? And I don't know if
you guys read a history book, but me and
my people, [laughter]
we ain't too fond of fields, man. Okay.
So, I'm I'm in my hotel room kind of
freaking out looking outside at all
these fields and I had to call my agents
and I said, "Hey, [laughter]
why the [\h__\h] DID YOU SEND me
to Springfield, Missouri?" They're like,
"Oh my god, it's amazing out there.
You're going to love it. You're going to
kill it." I said, "They're going TO KILL
ME, OKAY? AND I don't want to [\h__\h]
die here. It's ugly." Yo. Yeah, man.
And they got their own Disneyland in
[\h__\h] uh Springfield, Missouri. They
got their own Disneyland. They just
don't call it Disneyland. They call it
Bass Pro Shop. Yeah. [laughter] It's the
biggest one in the country. They're so
proud of it. Kept telling me all about
it. Yeah. Three stories in an aquarium.
Yeah. You got to go to our Bass Pro
Shop. Know the [\h__\h] I don't, homie. What
the [\h__\h] about me? Says Bass Pro Shop.
[\h__\h] out of my face, dog.
Why don't you go to our Bass Pro Shop?
Cuz I seen the movie Get Out. That's why
I go to Bass Pro Shop. [cheering] Think
I want some teacup [\h__\h] coming up to me
talking about you like fish.
[laughter]
Different layer of white.
I [\h__\h] with a lot of white [\h__\h] you
know? Like I'm one of those black dudes
that gets called white all the [\h__\h]
time. Yeah, rightfully so. I [\h__\h] get
it. Yeah, you know, and I used to get
mad when people would call me white boy
and [\h__\h] man. And then I realized it's
hard fighting for how black you are
while rocking a Pearl Jam t-shirt. Yeah.
Yeah. Storming off to a Jeep Wrangler.
Yeah, I know. [laughter]
4x4 unlimited sport. Come on now. Yeah.
Yeah. Jeep wave. It's a culture and I'm
part of it. Yeah.
[laughter] I'd be kicking [\h__\h] on the
way out, too, as I'm mad because that's
how white dudes get mad. They always
kicking [\h__\h] on the way out. They be
like, "Fuck you."
Yeah. Y'all seen it. Yeah. And that's
why they're punters.
Let that sink in.
No, man. Yeah. I I mean, like, I love
punk and hardcore music. That's like my
[\h__\h] I love punk and hardcore music,
you know? And here's the thing. I really
like the music, but I'm not the biggest
fan of the shows sometimes, you know?
Sometimes it's a different layer of
white.
I went and saw one of my favorite bands,
right? And I was super stoked on seeing
this band because it was my first time.
And they're on stage playing. And then
all of a sudden, out of nowhere, the
lead singer just started spitting on
everybody in the crowd. And I'm looking
at everybody just take this [\h__\h] And
I'm like, "Yo,
we should [\h__\h] him up. LET'S BEAT HIS
ASS, MAN. [\h__\h] up that mohawk, steal
those Doc Martin boots, and resell them
like Jordans. Yeah, they got good resale
value." [laughter]
So I was like, "Fuck this. I'm enjoying
myself in the back. So, I go to the back
to enjoy myself, right? Well, the thing
about punk and hardcore music is like we
got anthems and we sing we sing along
together, you know what I mean? And they
start playing the big bangers. So, I go
up to sing with everybody trying to
dodge this spit
and this dude spit into the crowd one
more time and that [\h__\h] landed right on
my [\h__\h] tongue.
[laughter]
And since then, I discovered Dave
Matthews Band. That's a great band right
there. Oh, come on. Yeah. Yeah. crashing
me with two tickets, [\h__\h] Okay,
that's the good hygiene whites over
there. I like them. Yeah, I know. Yeah,
they just wear open toe sandals and
[\h__\h] I'm I'm cool with that. Yeah. All
right. And they got black people in the
band. They had a black dude playing
violin and [\h__\h] Yeah. Yeah. He was just
out there like Yeah. I was like, that's
good. Hell yeah. Did you know we did
that, brother?
Yeah. So, I've been out here in Los
Angeles, you know, like five years now.
I got black friends and [\h__\h] Yeah. And
like these dudes, they, you know,
they're they're real witted and [\h__\h]
you know. They grew up in this area
called Compton, right? And uh Yep. I've
heard of Compton for sure. Yep. Yep. In
songs. Yep. Only in songs.
The funny thing about Compton is when
they talk about Compton in the songs,
they say it's so aggressive, they just
be like Compton, Compton, Compton. And
we never shout Phoenix like that at all.
We do not. What? [laughter]
We're like Phoenix. Jump on it. Jump on
it. Jump on it. Yeah. That's our state
song.
Yeah.
Yeah. Yeah.
You know, he's changed my lingo. The
lingo is like pretty wild, you know.
Like the thing is like G. Everything's
like gta say G and you know like and I
don't know what it means you know and
it's it's always aggressive you know
like G you know and every time they're
like yeah yeah Chappelle want you man
stop playing and just say that [\h__\h] and
I'm like [laughter] well G I'm a little
lost all right freaking a dude she
lordy morty [\h__\h]
[laughter] I'm trying to be your friend
but it's [\h__\h] difficult golly
where's the friendship bracelet already.
Mhm. [laughter]
What's wild is like even though I get
made fun of for like I get called white
boy and [\h__\h] but I also I get made fun
of for my dark complexion, too. And like
my dark complexion, that's my favorite
thing about me. You know what I mean? It
is. Hell yeah. Okay, black people. Hell
yeah.
Some of the white people are like, "Oh,
[laughter]
I say that because when I was younger,
people would make fun of how dark I am,
try to make me feel insecure about it
and [\h__\h] They used to call me names,
dog. They used to call me black as hell
Chappelle. Jokes on them. I like that
name.
Thanks, Frank. [laughter]
I killed a game with my darkness. I use
that [\h__\h] to my advantage. Always have.
Especially when I was in school. [\h__\h]
Listen, anytime a teacher was showing a
video in class, that was my perfect
opportunity to sneak the [\h__\h] out.
I [\h__\h] with school that much. I like,
"Oh my god, Miss Johnson, we watching
Bill Nye, the science guy again. That's
crazy." [laughter]
You know, Miss Johnson, you always been
one of my fave
>> [laughter]
[laughter]
>> That's my [\h__\h]
And I tell y'all one thing. [laughter]
If the rest of the lights turn on this
[\h__\h] I'm robbing every single
one of y'all. Y'all look nice. Hey yo,
that's my time, man. Y'all have a
blessing. [applause and cheering]
What's popping, Christians?
>> Yeah. Oh, easy. [laughter]
Oh, I feel good, dude. I do. I do wish I
was naked right now.
>> I do. No, y'all didn't pay enough money
for that. He's like, "Yeah, anybody with
me?"
I do, man. I grew up in a house full of
women, so I was naked all the time.
Okay. I'd show up to the dinner table,
titties over the ters.
[laughter]
What are y'all thankful for? Huh?
My mom's like that your dad's getting
custody.
[laughter]
You take those little B cupups over to
his trailer. [laughter]
Get out of my double wide.
It's a house.
I love being in LA, man. I love
traveling. I think one of my favorite
parts about traveling is eating fast
food. Love that [\h__\h] dude. Panera is my
favorite cuz they're trying to be
something they're not. And I'm here for
that [\h__\h]
They have an open concept kitchen and
the only thing they have to cook with is
a microwave.
[laughter] That's so embarrassing, bro.
The worst is when you order steak cuz
they're like, "How would you like that
cooked?" I'm like on two.
[laughter]
I don't know. We'll just put it in
there. Let it spin around and toss it to
me like a dog. We know why I'm here.
[laughter]
I also love traveling cuz as a kid it
was traumatic. And an adult I can do my
thing, right? Like as a kid, my granny
never had time to pull off on an exit if
I had to pee. If I had to pee, she would
pull over on the side of the road, pop
open a couple of doors,
and 11-year-old me would be like, "Can
they see me? [laughter]
Am I hidden?" My granny's like, "You're
good." And then a trucker would come by.
[laughter]
I'm like, "Great, he saw something."
She's like, "Get your ass up. We got to
get to Six Flags.
Like at 7:00 a.m., they open at noon.
[laughter]
I grew up very southern, okay? Like, I
can't go back to my hometown and order
unsweet tea where I'm from. Everybody
would be like, "What in the liberal
hell?
[laughter]
Who ordered this?" I'm like, "I don't
know. We should kill them."
I'm with you guys. [laughter]
We had like 12 dogs at a time. They
weren't our dogs. People would drive by
the farm, roll down the window, and Art,
just toss them out. [laughter]
I'm like, "We don't do names here. Get
in line if you want grub."
My grandpa tried to make him family.
He'd put them up at the table and be
like, "Now
let your sister
lick from your plate."
I'm like, "That is not my sister. My
sister's in rehab.
I know the meth kind of makes her look
like a Chihuahua
cheer for meth. Okay, [laughter]
she's got two more teeth in 507. Okay,
it's how we tell them apart.
I grew up with an older sister. Anybody
else older sister?
>> Yeah. You hear that? Yeah.
Trauma, bro. [laughter]
She must be here or something. You were
like, "It was fine. It was fun." Yeah.
>> [laughter]
>> My sister prepared me for prison. Okay.
I would just be chilling in the front
yard. My sister would come up, grab my
ponytail, and just start fighting me,
dude. [laughter]
And the whole time she's like, "I only
let you borrow my pants cuz you look fat
in them." [laughter]
I'm like, "You're my only friend.
Please, God, let me go." [laughter]
My mom's on the front porch with a
whiskey coat like, "Figure it out.
>> [laughter]
>> Swear to God, if you're still fighting
when SVU comes on, I'm going to be
pissed.
And that's why I love public fighting
today, bro. I do. My favorite is road
rage. Okay. I'm an aggressive driver,
which means I'm the best driver.
I hate when people get in my car and
they're screaming,
crying like, "WE WANT TO LIVE."
>> [laughter]
>> I'M LIKE, "YOU CALLED THIS UBER, MY GUY.
Maybe save up your old pennies and buy
your own car
cuz we're going to be running from the
cops."
I'm not good at road rage either. This
girl and her boyfriend cut me and my
boyfriend off and I was like, "Pull up
to her car, babe.
[laughter]
Pull up to her car. I'm going to do
something freaking crazy."
And I hadn't planned anything. So I was
just like
just all teeth. My boyfriend's like,
"Where'd you learn that?" I'm like, "My
granny, [laughter]
you ever seen a truck driver?" No.
[laughter]
My therapist tries to help me. She was
like, "You know what might help with the
road rage is if you listen to opera
music."
No, [\h__\h] Cuz now instead of wanting to
kill people, I just have a soundtrack
for it.
They cut me off at a red light. I'm
like,
[laughter]
"Get out the car. I'll beat your ass."
Oh, [\h__\h] They're really doing it. Run.
Run. [laughter]
Is anyone here with their best friend
tonight? We got Besty Westies.
>> No. There's no way. Five of
that was late. Okay,
that whole I feel like three of you have
a group chat the other four aren't a
part of.
There's no way you're all best friends.
I love that. I always feel mature until
I meet my best friend's other best
friend, [laughter]
which isn't a [\h__\h] thing. Okay,
I'm always like, defend your spot, the
pack, you know?
And it always happens when I'm
introducing myself. So I'm like, "Hi,
I'm Amber and our periods sync up.
Can you compete with science?
[laughter]
Keep it moving.
I'm actually on my period right now."
Look, [laughter]
he was like, "Aha." Okay. Like you just
learned a fact about space. You're like,
"That's crazy." Okay, I believe it cuz I
have no idea.
Usually guys look away. I'm like, "It's
not airborne. You can't catch it.
You're not even blinking. I love that
you guys are uncancellable. [laughter]
I rarely talk about being on my period
cuz I'm embarrassed by it, bro. I can
loudly ask for cocaine, but I have to
whisper for a pad.
And whispering for a pad is not cute.
This is the sign. I'd be like, "Do you
have something I can put my panties?"
[laughter]
You got a diaper that would cover my ass
crack.
No, I'm a liberal. I'll freele bleed.
You know what I'm saying? The bush will
catch most of it.
Oh, don't owe me. You got a hairy ass
back.
My mom like mom's like hype up periods
too. It's so weird. Like you get your
period, you go in the bathroom, all of a
sudden you're bleeding. My mom comes in
and she's like, [gasps]
"Do you want to get Chinese food?"
[laughter]
Like, why are you offering me my last
meal? [laughter]
I think the worst part about periods are
dogs, bro.
[laughter]
Cuz they're the first ones to rat you
out.
Man's best friend hates women.
[laughter]
You go to a party, you're trying to be
chill, you know, and here's that dog
right up there.
This is the one, mom.
She's rare.
[laughter]
I'm like, you were adopted, you little
[\h__\h]
You're not even full breed golden
doodle. They forg. [laughter]
Okay. I love cat. Yes, ma'am. Yes. Love
cats. I love the way they love. They're
like, "Do I love you? Do I not?
>> [laughter]
>> I'm going to pee in your shoe.
I'm like, "Dad,
you're both hairy and can't aim. PAPA,
YOU'VE COME BACK."
But this cat that I have, bro, he's
weird. Okay. He loves to watch me have
sex.
Yeah. He lo He's so fat. never moves
until I'm about to go boink. AND THEN
HE'S LIKE, I WANT TO SEE.
[laughter]
Let me in. We have to borrow the door.
He's got his paw under there.
Just looking for a nipple or a ball
sack, you know, [laughter]
both the color of Atlantic salmon, so he
feels like he's in the wild, you know,
[laughter]
just two whites in there thrashing
around.
Eventually, we let him in. We're like,
"Get your ass in here." He comes in like
a little hype man.
He puts his little paw on my boyfriend's
back. He's like, "Keep going, Dad.
[laughter]
If we get through this, we can both have
wet food."
[laughter]
I love my boyfriend. Are we any singles
in here?
>> Oh, wow. [laughter]
Someone goes
like I'm single, but I looked around and
I'm not, you know,
not here. Not tonight. [laughter]
I love singles. I'm a good matchmaker.
My parents got together because of me.
[laughter]
I am with someone though and
unfortunately he's attractive and that
was a mistake. Okay, you got to date
ugly. All right, [laughter]
you really do. Ugly people roll with the
punches. My boyfriend woke up one
morning and was like, "Great news. We
just won a raffle to climb a mountain in
California." I was like, "Sounds like we
lost a raffle, my guy.
You got a mouse in your pocket? Who the
[\h__\h] is we?"
He's the kind of hot where girls will
pretend that we're not together just so
they can have a chance, right? Like
we'll be at a grocery store. will have a
cart full of groceries and this girl
will be like, "Oh my god."
Are you going to eat all that by
yourself?
[laughter]
My nipples are hard.
I like to play along. I'm like, "The
double stuffed Oreos are mine."
[laughter]
She's like, "Oh my god, you take care of
your sister."
My name's Amber Audrey. You guys have
been dope. Thank you so much. Anyone
balding? [laughter]
Anyone going through this hell?
One guy in the back. Shily. Yes, sir.
Did it start during the pandemic?
>> Many years before that.
>> Many years before that. My friend.
[laughter]
This is how bald people talk to balding
people.
My friend, you have many years of
hardship ahead of you. [laughter]
May the wind be at your back. [laughter]
[laughter]
I [\h__\h] got dude. Check it out. Oh,
[\h__\h] you. [laughter]
[\h__\h] all of you.
I hate LA so much. I swear to God. I I
show my bald spot all across the
country. LA people are like, "Oh, you
piece of [\h__\h]
You balding [\h__\h] [laughter]
Your life's over. You're going to die
alone.
I show my bald spot in Milwaukee.
They're like, "You're the hottest guy
here. [laughter]
You're the hottest guy we've ever seen.
So, please, please leave." You know,
[laughter]
I hate B cuz it's up here. I can't see
it. Does that make sense? It's happening
above my like if I was missing a leg or
an arm, I would remember. I would know
that first thing. I would see it in
[snorts] the morning. I would see it.
But I forget I'm balding. I just
remember when shitty things happen to
me. That's when I like I'll lock myself
out of my apartment and I'll be like,
"And I'm balding." YOU KNOW
[laughter]
that's the moment
when God's like also that is happening
at the same time.
I was raised Muslim. My dad's a Jew who
became a Muslim. So he's the first one
to do that. [laughter]
Pretty revolutionary man.
He's not good at it, by the way. He's
still Jew. You can't just not be Jewish.
Like he's Jewish at heart. Like he's
Muslim, but he's Jewey about it. He's
like a [laughter]
He's a Jewy Muslim.
Hard to describe what that mean. Like
he'll fast for Ramadan just till noon,
you know. [laughter]
Just till lunch.
He's like, I'm going to eat. We're like,
go for it, Jeff. You know, do your
thing.
Jews are, if you're Jewish, this is a
crazy thing. You're at the end of every
conspiracy theory.
Like people think Jews did every not
just banks in Hollywood. Like I travel,
people are like crop circles. That was
Jews. [laughter]
That was also Jews. I'm like, first I
don't think they don't like yard work.
First of all, [laughter]
I don't think they're doing crop
circles. Also, I thought that was alien.
Wasn't that aliens? They're like, yeah,
we thought so. Then we thought something
weirder, you know? [laughter]
We thought something we understand less.
We went to Jews.
They went from aliens to Jews.
The one thing they still think is aliens
is the pyramids in Egypt. [laughter]
And that was Jews, you know.
So, [applause]
give them that. You know
what else is going on? Is anyone single,
you guys?
>> The girls are happy about it. [laughter]
I hate when guys are like, "Fuck yeah, I
love being single. [laughter] Do
whatever I want all the time. What'd you
do today?" I jacked off and cried.
[laughter]
So, did it on my terms, though, you
know? [laughter]
Didn't have a girl tell me I couldn't
jack off and cry all day. So, that was
[laughter] good.
I have been in a relationship before.
You have to do stuff. [laughter]
Shut up.
I said it wrong. [laughter]
You do have to do stuff you don't want
to do. Like every relationship I'm in,
my girlfriend's like, "Let's get a
couple's massage.
Let's go do that." And I'm like, "Okay."
Every time I'm like, "Yeah, sure. Sounds
nice." And then you go you go in the
back, you know, at the the massage
parlor to like a private room and it's
like really sexy, you know, and then
they send in a guy and a girl to massage
you. And my girlfriend gets the guy to
massage her every time, which is like I
don't want. He's like a professional
toucher,
you know what I mean? And I have to
witness it. I have to w I have to
witness a professional touch my
girlfriend for an hour. And I can't see
it cuz you have to put your head in the
hole.
You know what I mean? You put your head
in the hole. We both have our heads in
the hole. But I [laughter]
I All I can do is hear her moan moaning
like sounds I've never heard her make.
[laughter]
I've never made her do that. Like
whatever that is.
And I can't see. I just hear her like,
"Oh." And I'm like, "Are you eating her
ass?" Like what?
It seems like she likes that
and I'm not enjoying it because my job I
have my head in the hole and I'm
listening to her come and I'm I'm
[laughter]
all I'm doing I'm just holding in a fart
for an hour.
[laughter]
That's my whole job
is she's just like oh and I'm just like
like don't [laughter]
and this woman's on top of me like
pushing air like down my back like going
that way and she's like you seem
stressed. I'm like I'm going to fart in
your face like [laughter]
your face is on top of my [\h__\h]
>> [laughter]
>> They don't play music you can fart to in
like it's it's like these long
harmonious tones.
I'm like I can't sneak it out, you know?
[laughter]
Give me some jazz, you know? Give me
give me something I can fart to.
[laughter]
And then they take out the hot stones,
you know? I'm like I'm going to [\h__\h]
everywhere. [laughter]
trying to break up. You're trying to end
this relationship. Is that the plan?
[laughter]
I don't have much time left
on this planet. [laughter]
I um poor. Is anyone poor?
[\h__\h] yeah. Rowdy group. [laughter]
I started doing this thing on my
Instagram. This is I I don't think
anyone could do this but me. I just
posted on my story. I said, "If you
Venmo me any amount of money, I will
scream in public." [laughter]
And people were like, "Sure."
People started set like people were
like, "We didn't know we needed this.
This is amazing. I make good money." I
would just scream in public and and tag
them in the video. [laughter] It was the
best job I ever had.
And this is the scream. So, imagine you
guys are in a coffee shop, okay? And I
just walk in,
[screaming]
[laughter]
just made five bucks. [laughter]
And it broke my mind cuz nobody gave a
[\h__\h] I don't know if that was a LA
thing. Like, I would just walk into
places and scream and people didn't
care. Like white people didn't care.
Especially white. If you walk into a
place and scream and there's white
people, they'll be on their phone and
then they'll look up and they'll be
like, "I'm not experiencing that."
Actually,
[laughter]
they're like, "That's not part of my
day. So, I'm just going to keep
Black dudes loved it. [laughter]
I don't know why. If I'd walk into a
place and scream and there's a black
dude, he'd be like, I [\h__\h] with that."
Yeah. [laughter]
And I kept that kept happening. I'm
like, why do black dudes love when I
scream in public so much? And then I was
like, oh, in his mind he's like, if I
was white, man, that's the [\h__\h] I would
do. [laughter]
Like, I found this pocket of white
privilege.
You could scream. You can walk around. I
walked into a bank and scream. They're
like, "Do you want a credit card? Like,
we'll give you [laughter]
I walked into an army recruitment center
and screamed. They're like, "We need
you. We can
>> [laughter]
>> We could use this.
I kept screaming. I kept doing it. I
went to the zoo dressed as a hot dog.
I don't know why. [laughter] I just got
my friend to film me. I just walked
around the zoo dressed as a hot dog
screaming and the kids [\h__\h] loved it.
[laughter]
I If you want a day, go to the zoo
dressed as a hot dog cuz every kid goes,
"Hi, hot dog."
I don't know why they have to [laughter]
there's something in their brain that's
like say hi hot dog to the hot dog
[clears throat] and I would say I'd say
hi hot dog and their dads would be like
what the [\h__\h] is that
I don't remember that that's part of the
zoo
got a hot dog says high hot dog
[laughter]
so then I was like I have to get in
trouble so I'm like I'm going to go
scream at the church of Scientology.
[laughter]
>> Yes. Thank you. It's a blue building.
You can go. You can just They They make
you sign in. I just write Tom Cruz.
[laughter]
I just spell it with a Z like it's
vegan, you know? Like,
but I walked in and I couldn't scream. I
looked at them and they scared me. Have
you seen them?
>> They don't blink. [laughter]
And they were like, "Can I help you?"
I'm like, "No, not at all.
I was going to scream, but I'm scared.
[laughter]
And I went back to my apartment and I
felt like a coward. And then I smoked a
little weed. And I'm like, I'm going
back. [laughter]
And I went back. I went to the Church of
Scient. I busted in the door
just [\h__\h] [laughter]
And they were like, "Sir, you have to
leave now." [laughter] And I was like,
"Yeah, obviously.
Obviously, that was the plan the whole
time. [laughter]
I wasn't going to walk in here and
scream and then be like, "So, what's it
about?" Like, "What do you guys do?"
[laughter] All right, that is my time.
Thank you so much, guys. [cheering]
Enjoy the rest OF THE SHOW. WOO. YOU
KNOW it
when you when you find your drugs
[laughter]
when you find your drugs in your stuff
like your drugs
the the temptation to do them is tenfold
[laughter]
you know it's something activate in you
where you just like this this is from
2011 I know it's no fentol in this you
[laughter] know
you just get hypnotized eyes. You one
minute you you going through a box you
haven't opened since two moves ago and
the next minute you googling does acid
expire and then [laughter]
you just on acid,
you know, [laughter] then you're like,
"Oh [\h__\h] I got a show." And then you're
[laughter] Yeah. you just stuck in the
wrong mindset for work, you know,
cuz you can't lie to yourself on certain
substances. You know what I figured out?
I I figured out why I turned off the
Amber Alerts, you know, and it's Oh,
yours are off, too, [\h__\h] Stop
playing [laughter]
out here being judgmental. Uh, you know,
cuz at first I thought it cuz I'm a
terrible person. It's like, oh, you
know, you get a notification and you're
like, oh, someone's thinking of me. And
then you grab your phone, you're like,
oh, it's just missing children. you
know, [laughter]
but the real reason I turned them off is
just because, you know, they never tell
you if they found them. And [laughter]
I just don't think the administration
should be able to inject suspense into
my life, [laughter]
right? With no conclusion. Like like
I did my part. I I went outside. I
looked for a silver Ford Focus.
[laughter]
No, I'd like an update.
I don't think that's too much to ask. I
pay taxes. [laughter]
Being real honest with myself.
[laughter]
You know what else? I real I realized
I'm not really against slavery.
Yeah. Yeah.
I did a lot of thinking and I realized
what I'm actually against is the chance
of me being a slave. [laughter]
That's what I actually have the energy
to stop from happening, right?
If they announced that they were
bringing slavery back next month, right?
Cuz Elon said it was more efficient.
[laughter]
And in the press conference, they were
like, you know, for obvious reasons,
black people don't have to do this one.
[laughter]
I would be like, "Well, let's hear all
the details [laughter]
[cheering]
before we jump to conclusions,
right?
[laughter]
We we could all use a little help around
the house."
[laughter]
See, all y'all fake [\h__\h] cuz cuz you
agree with me, but we just we fake now
cuz the cuz young people look terrible.
This is the fakest generation. Y'all are
y'all just a [\h__\h] generation of HR
ladies. You know this [laughter]
just walking around. That's not a purple
hat
cuz you young [\h__\h] don't know
this. But like the way because of y'all
the way everyone has to act now all the
time. You used to only have to do that
at work.
[applause]
[laughter]
You know, in the in in the in the '9s,
you know, you you could clock out and be
like, "Fucking ass,
[laughter]
and it was still wrong, but you wouldn't
lose your job,
[laughter]
you know? Now everybody got to be fake,
y'all." If like if I asked everybody in
here, "Hey, are you cool with slavery?"
All y'all would be like, "No, of course
not." Especially if you thought I was
recording you for social media,
[laughter]
then you got to put a little extra on
it. That's the preposterism.
>> [laughter]
>> You know, you got to really
keep up your public image,
[laughter] but you fake as [\h__\h] You
fake because listen, yeah, of course
you'll say that you're not okay with
slavery, but you live your life like you
could care less. [laughter]
There's more slaves now than ever.
Slavery isn't over. It's just not here,
right? And we all benefit from it. And
you know that deep down inside. That's
why every time you get a good deal, you
feel a little guilty.
>> Yeah. Yeah. You whisper it to people.
You run out the store. My god.
10 peaches for a dollar. How do they do
it?
You know exactly how they [\h__\h] do it,
don't you? [laughter] You know precisely
how it's done.
[laughter]
This is what I do. I I I do drugs. I
ponder.
Um, you know something I don't think I'm
ever going to figure out is why women
don't apologize. [laughter]
I don't know how y'all keep getting away
with it, but you're never [\h__\h] sorry.
You don't [laughter] you don't you don't
apologize. You rationalize,
right? It's what most of you are doing
right now. Instead of listening to my
most likely to be brilliant take on the
matter, [laughter]
you sitting there saying to yourself, "I
say sorry all the time. I say sorry more
than he does."
>> [laughter]
>> And and the thing is, I give you that. I
think women say sorry a thousand times
more than men do. But I'm on to you
hoes. [laughter]
Yeah. See, you you've been patting your
stats and we've been letting it slide.
[laughter]
The only reason you say sorry way more
than men do is cuz you always saying
sorry, but only when no woman was asking
you to apologize. [laughter]
Yeah. I watch you all the time. I watch
you. You you y'all will say sorry for
existing. You will walk into a room that
you definitely belong in and go sorry.
[laughter]
I made it.
Some of you will apologize for something
awesome you did. Baby, I'm so sorry. I
woke up before you and made breakfast
and finished the taxes.
[laughter]
Thanks.
But as soon as there's any
accountability,
oh that's the new joint. Women, women
love accountability.
Before 2015, nobody said that there
wasn't coaching youth sports.
But I realized like when women say
accountability, they talking about their
ability to hold you accountable.
[laughter]
soon as you try to hold them account.
Yo, hey babe, why did you max out the
credit card and um [\h__\h] my COUSIN
[laughter]
being like, I'm a I'm a Scorpio in
retrograde. I'm a rising [laughter]
patriarch,
right?
And some of y'all want to dismiss this
as misogyny. I can feel it. I can hear
the little whispers. I'm misogyny. What
a shanka. He's from Austin, Texas.
>> [laughter]
>> Austin misogyny.
And here's the thing. This is the
furthest thing from misogyny. This is
actually feminism.
Yeah. This is feminism at its highest
level.
>> Yeah. Yeah. This is feminism at a level
that your small woman brain can barely
comprehend.
[laughter]
[applause]
[laughter] Guys, I'm I'm kidding. We
have the same size brains. Okay? That's
just science.
[laughter]
No, but this is actually feminism. And
and and and I'll prove it. I'll prove it
to you. Any any long-term couples here?
Been together like say seven plus.
>> Anybody?
>> You guys how long?
>> 16 years.
>> 16 years. Okay. And what's your And
what's your name, ma'am?
>> Darcy.
>> Darcy. And what's your name, sir?
>> Mike.
>> Mike, do me a favor, Mike. I'mma ask
Darcy a question. Don't say nothing and
don't look at him. [laughter]
Okay. Hey, hey, Darcy. In 16 years, how
many times have you sincerely
apologized to Mike?
You don't know. Okay. No, no, no. That
That's okay. She's on the spot. Okay.
Let me let me ask you an easier
question. What was the last thing you
sincerely apologized to Mike for?
And that brings me to my point,
[laughter] right?
Is
No, no, no, no. BECAUSE THIS IS WHY THIS
IS ACTUALLY FEMINISM. I'm going show
you. Because I learned everything about
apologies from listening to women,
right? In this modern era of social
media, ever since it came about,
whenever a famous man get in trouble and
try to apologize in public, it be women
in the comments going, "That's not even
a real apology." [laughter]
A real apology consists of A, B, and C.
He's a little low on the beat for my
taste. [laughter]
Right. I've seen that comment a thousand
times. of you, man. And I read all them
shits cuz I said, "You know what? I want
to be a good apologizer." [laughter]
Right? And this is what I learned from
reading all the women's comments. I
learned, and ladies correct me if I'm
wrong. I learned that an apology, even
if it's perfect,
is meaningless if it's not followed by
changed behavior.
>> Amen.
>> Right? So, if you don't remember what
you did, then you wasn't [\h__\h] sorry,
were you? [laughter]
No,
you just said sorry and walked away like
I apologize all the time. [laughter]
This is my ex problem. Never want to
apologize. Always want to get married.
[laughter]
When are we getting married? Be nice to
me. Have you Have you tried being nice?
[laughter]
Yeah. It's like you do you y'all love to
demand marriage like you just owed that.
Like you not even a good roommate.
[laughter]
Yeah. Won't you stop planning weddings
until you learn to stop putting short
[\h__\h] in the fridge where tall [\h__\h] is
supposed to be? [laughter]
It drives me insane. [laughter]
Things are have a play. Every time I
find a Red Bull in a butter dish, I want
to bash your [\h__\h] skull up.
[laughter]
Seriously,
every kind of fridge at every economic
level has a place for the butter. That's
the one thing nobody in the world should
be on the hunt for.
[laughter]
And oh, I'm I some I heard a little
whisper that I Oh, who hurt him?
[laughter]
I [\h__\h] hat I hate that lazy response.
I'm not afraid of commitment. I'll have
y'all know. I'm going to tell y'all
something that she don't even know until
this airs.
[laughter]
I bought a diamond a year before we
broke up.
>> Yeah. And she never got it because I
taped it to the bottom of the Brida
filter that she never refilled.
Yeah. She's a [\h__\h] terrible human.
Listen.
[laughter] Yeah. Yeah.
That's why
[laughter]
That's why I think the next uh the next
person I get real serious about
um is going to definitely have to be a
Cowboys fan, you know. Yeah. Yeah. Cuz
you can tell them anything, [laughter]
you know. It's like when are we getting
married? This our year, babe. For sure.
[laughter]
I'm Ryan Simpson.
>> [music]